Guide to the Charles Davis Jameson Papers, Photographs and Photograph Albums, 1887-1919 and undated RL.11422
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photograph albums
  - Photograph album 2, 1890s
    - Terraced landscape with crops, 1890s; 5.625 x 2.75 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0107)
      Page 24. copy of RL11422-P-0106
    - Chinese house with terraced cropland in the back, 1890s; 3.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0108)
      大户庭院，远处是梯田
    - Terraced landscape with river, 1890s; 5.875 x 4.125 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0109)
      梯田和山谷中的河流
    - Loess Plateau, 1890s; 5.875 x 4.25 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0110)
      黄土高原
    - Terraced cropland and houses, 1890s; 5.5 x 3.625 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0111)
      梯田和农舍
    - Houses built into side of a hill, 1890s; 3.625 x 2.75 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0112)
      窑洞
    - Farmstead on side of hill, 1890s; 5.25 x 4.125 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0113)
      山坡上的农舍
    - Fengsheng Si, Buddhist Relics Pagoda, 1890s; 6 x 4.125 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0114)
      奉圣寺舍利生塔
    - Waterfalls, 1890s; 6 x 4.25 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0115)
      河流和瀑布
    - Four male Chinese beggars, 1890s; 5.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0116)
      四名男乞丐
    - Miners working on coal mine, 1898; 3.75 x 2.75 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0117)
      煤矿上干活的人们
      Page 29. Both Jameson and Shockley worked for the Perkin Syndicate in China.. duplicate of William Hillman Shockley image: RL01177-P-0705
    - A group of Chinese peasants, 1890s; 5.25 x 4.875 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0118)
      农民们
    - Chinese man with donkey carrying coal, 1890s; 3.75 x 2.875 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0119)
      人牵着运煤的毛驴
      Page 29. Both Jameson and Shockley worked for the Perkin Syndicate in China. Duplicate of William Hillman Shockley image: RL01177-P-0730
    - Four Chinese workers with rice bowls, 1890s; 2.625 x 3.875 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0120)
      端着碗站着吃饭的四个人
      Page 29. Both Jameson and Shockley worked for the Perkin Syndicate in China. Duplicate of William Hillman Shockley image: RL01177-P-0810
    - Iron miner, April 1898, 1890s; 3.75 x 2.75 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0121)
      铁矿工，1898年4月
      Page 29. Both Jameson and Shockley worked for the Perkin Syndicate in China. Duplicate of William Hillman Shockley image of RL01177-P-0729
    - Chinese man on horseback, 1890s; 2.75 x 4 in. (Box 8, Album 2, Print RL11422-P-0122)
      马上戴帽的男子
      Page 29. Both Jameson and Shockley worked for the Perkin Syndicate in China. Duplicate of William Hillman Shockley image: RL01177-P-0826
  - Photograph album 3, 1890s
    - Track leading to mountain, 1890s; 8 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0123)
      山路，路旁的高山
    - Buildings and houses in the mountains, 1890s; 8 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0124)
      山顶的建筑和山腰的房屋
    - Farmstead in mountain gap, 1890s; 7.75 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0125)
      大山和山间的梯田
    - Farmstead in the mountains, 1890s; 8 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0126)
      山间的梯田
    - Single structure at top of mountain, 1890s; 8 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0127)
      孤山顶上的小屋
    - Structures at top of mountain, 1890s; 8.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0128)
      大山和山顶上的房屋
    - River running through steep valley, 1890s; 8 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0129)
      山谷中的河流
    - Pools of water in riverbed between mountains, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0130)
      山谷中的河滩
    - Chinese peasant walking on mountain road, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0131)
      山路上行走的农夫
    - Farmstead on a hill, 1890s; 8 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0132)
      山包上的农舍
    - Three Chinese boats docked, with Charles Davis Jameson on boat at right?, 1890s; 8 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0133)
      河边的三艘帆船，右边船上站着詹美生（？）
    - Group of men on horseback in front of supply train, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0134)
      岸边的探测队，骑马的队员们，后边的大车
    - Four Chinese boats docked along river, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0135)
      岸边的四艘帆船
    - Terraced landscape, with mountains behind, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0136)
      梯田，大山
    - Three Chinese boats docked, with their crews, 1890s; 7.875 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0137)
      岸边的三艘帆船，船上休憩的人们
    - Sorghum field, village in the background, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0138)
      高粱地，后面的村落
    - Temple halls, 1890s; 8.25 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0139)
      寺院
    - Three Chinese men in front of two carts, 1890s; 8 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0140)
      两辆大车，坐着休息的三个赶车人
    - Living room of Chinese house, with mix of Western and Chinese objects, 1890s; 8 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0141)
      起居室内，中式建筑，西式家具
    - Woman reading letter while seated at a writing desk in a Western house, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0142)
      西式房屋内，坐在桌边读信的妇女
    - Group of Westerners in front of Chinese building, including a detachment of troops, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0143)
      中式房屋前的一群西方人合影，包括两排军官士兵
    - Group of Westerners in front of a Western building, including one Chinese woman holding a baby, and a detachment of troops, with machine gun in foreground, 1890s; 7.875 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0144)
      西式房屋前的一群西方人合影，包括抱着小孩的中国保姆，两边的士兵和前边的大炮
    - Detachment of troops in formation in front of Western house, with machine gun in foreground, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0145)
      士兵们列队，一侧的大炮的后面的西式以及中式建筑
    - Western man sitting on porch of Chinese house, 1890s; 8.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0146)
      中式庭院屋前坐着的西方人
    - Western house, with porch, from street, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0147)
      西式房屋，门廊
    - Western woman standing at entrance to Chinese house, from distance, 1890s; 8 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0148)
      中式庭院内，屋前站着的一位西方妇女
    - Three Westerners at Chinese house, from garden, 1890s; 8.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0149)
      中式庭院中的三个西方人
    - Living room of Chinese house, with focus on the mantel, 1890s; 8.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0150)
      中式房屋内，中西式家具和中间用于祭拜的地方
    - Living room of Chinese house, with focus on the piano, 1890s; 8.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0151)
      中式房屋内，中西式家具和一侧的钢琴
    - Five Westerners gathered with some Chinese on a porch, 1890s; 7.625 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0152)
      五个西方人和一些中国人的合影
    - Two Western women at a gate, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0153)
      两位西方妇女在月亮门处合影
      Page 31.
    - Western woman in Chinese clothing, standing next to table in front of a screen, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0154)
      身着中式服装的西方妇女站在屏风前，一侧的小桌上放了一些古董
    - Outer wall of Chinese temple, 1890s; 7.875 x 7.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0155)
      寺院外墙
    - Small Chinese house and trees, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.75 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0156)
      小房屋和一旁的大树
    - Railroad bridge over river, with sign, and city wall in distance, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0157)
      河上的铁路桥，路标和远处的城墙
    - Single Chinese boat, docked with crew aboard and some supplies and donkeys on shore, 1890s; 8.125 x 5.875 in. (Box 8, Album 3, Print RL11422-P-0158)
      河边停靠的大船，船上的货物人员和岸边的驴子
  - Photograph album 4, undated (Box 6)
  - Photograph album 5, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album containing 72 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, all 3.375 x 2.25-inches. Topics mainly include waterways and boats, with some landscapes and a few images of Chinese people and Westerners.
  - Photograph album 6, undated (Box 6)
    Undated phototograph album containing 72 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, all 3.375 x 2.25 inches. Photograph subjects include landscapes, engineering projects, waterways, street scenes in rural China, and caravans of various types.
  - Photograph album 7, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album containing 36 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, around 5.75 x 4.25 inches. Subjects include mainly Chinese and Westerners, many in groups or having portraits taken, including one photograph of Charles Davis Jameson in a voluminous robe; there are also images of rural scenes, missionaries, houses for Westerners, and a monk with weapons.
  - Photograph album 8, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album featuring 72 uncaptioned and quite faded black-and-white photographs, sized 2.25 x 3 inches. Subjects include street scenes and groups of people in cities, conveyances, rural scenes, and waterways and boats.
  - Photograph album 9, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album containing 72 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, sized around 5.375 x 2.25 inches. Topics in the photographs include waterways and boats, engineering projects, as well as street and rural scenes.
  - Photograph album 10, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album containing 72 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, sized around 3.375 x 2.25 inches. The photographs were likely taken in Shanxi province, and include street scenes and images of waterways and boats.
  - Photograph album 11, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album contains 45 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, ranging in size from 3.75 x 2.75 inches to 5.75 x 4.25 inches. The photographs were taken in Shanxi province and feature contoured landscapes, temples and other buildings, street scenes, and engineering projects.
  - Photograph album 12, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album features 36 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, ranging in size from 5.375 x 4.25 inches to 5.75 x 4.25 inches. Many of the photographs were taken in Beijing, and scenes include the Confucian Temple and Great Wall, along with landscapes, and images taken in courtyards.
  - Photograph album 13, undated (Box 6)
    Undated photograph album features 72 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs, most about 3.375 x 2.5 inches. Photographs were taken in Beijing, and include the Ancient Observatory and Legation Compound, along with images of horseracing and street scenes.
  - Photograph album 14, 1898 and undated (Box 6)
    Photograph album dated 1898 containing 65 black-and-white photographs, mostly 3.375 x 2.5 inches, and many with captions in pencil. The images are based in Beijing, and feature horse races; a train station; residences of Westerners; street scenes, including funerals; the Marco Polo Bridge, as well as images of the Coal region West of the city.
  - Photograph album 15, undated (Box 8)
    Japanese commercial accordion photograph album featuring 24 hand-tinted photographs, most about 5.5 x 3.625 inches. Phtotographs are uncaptioned. Images feature buildings, landscapes, waterways, with interior scenes showing Japanese women and men individually and in groups, with several portraits.
  - Photograph album 16, undated (Box 7)
    Undated photograph album featuring 50 uncaptioned black-and-white photographs. Subjects include landscapes, buildings, Westerners and Chinese in groups, other groups of Chinese, waterways and boats, street scenes, groups of Western children, and religious bas reliefs. Album has been disbound.
  - Photograph album 17, 1890s
    - Group of five Chinese women beside a road, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0159)
      路边的五个妇女
    - Buildings along waterway, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0160)
      远处河岸上的房屋
    - Three Chinese boats, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0161)
      河上的三只帆船
    - Chinese town, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0162)
      村镇
    - Canal gate (distant), 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0163)
      河上闸门（远影）
    - Pedestrian bridge over canal, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0164)
      河闸上的人行桥
    - Canal gate (close), 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0165)
      河上闸门（近影）
    - Group of Chinese men along a road, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0166)
      乡绅们路边合影
    - Six Chinese boats, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0167)
      河上的六艘船只
    - Chinese ships docked, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0168)
      停靠在岸边的帆船
    - Houses and crowds lining the river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0169)
      岸边的房屋和迎送的队伍
    - Unloading a ferry, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0170)
      乘客们走下渡船
    - Chinese boat docked, with sailors, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0171)
      停在岸边的帆船和船上的水手们
    - Crowd waiting on bank, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0172)
      岸边等待的人群
    - One Chinese boat under sail, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0173)
      河上扬帆的船只
    - Structures on the water, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0174)
      建在水上的棚屋
    - Crowded Chinese boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0175)
      河上满载乘客的帆船
    - Crowded Chinese boat (closeup), 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0176)
      河上满载乘客的帆船（近影）
    - Wharf, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0177)
      码头
    - Passing through canal gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0178)
      河道转弯处
    - Flooded field, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0179)
      河水泛滥
    - Chinese boat, docked, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0180)
    - Chinese boat, docked, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0181)
      Page 6. Version of RL11422-P-0180
    - Men waiting on wharf, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0182)
      站在码头等待的人们
    - Washing alongside river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0183)
      河边洗涤
    - Bend in river, seen from hillside, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0184)
      远望河水交汇处
    - Small Chinese boats, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0185)
      河面上的船只
    - Chinese boat, with flag and sailors, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0186)
      河上的帆船，桅杆上飘扬的旗子
    - City Overview, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0187)
      城镇全景
    - Children along the river, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0188)
      河岸边的孩童
    - Washing along a pedestrian bridge in town, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0189)
      村镇河上小桥边洗涤的人们
    - Wall hangings in Chinese house, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0190)
      堂屋里挂着的画像
    - Four Chinese men on and near a wall, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0191)
      靠墙边的四个人
    - Stone bridge over river, with seven arches, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0192)
      河上的七孔桥
    - Sheaves of bamboo (?) with a band at left, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0193)
      河边垛起来的竹竿（？），一旁的乐队
    - Deck of Chinese boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0194)
      甲板上坐着的人们
    - Tributary from bend in river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0195)
      大河转弯处远观
      Page 10. Version of RL11422-P-0184
    - Chinese boat loaded with bamboo, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0196)
      河上装满竹竿的帆船
    - River at a distance, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0197)
      大河远观
    - Crop along river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0198)
      河边的庄稼
    - Chinese boat with flag and sailors, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0199)
      Page 11. Version of RL11422-P-0186
    - Three Westerners outside brick house, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0200)
      屋外的三个外国人
    - Russian ? soldiers outside building, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0201)
      俄罗斯（？）士兵站在屋外
    - Russian ? soldiers outside building (distance), 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0202)
      俄罗斯（？）士兵站在屋外（远影）
    - Crowd of Russians?, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0203)
      一群俄罗斯（？）人
    - Chinese town from distance, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0204)
      城镇远眺
    - Rapids, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0205)
      激流
    - Loading a boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0206)
      装船
    - Crowd of Russians?, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0207)
    - Chinese boat under sail, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0208)
      扬帆行驶的船只
    - Chinese boat with three flags, officers and soldiers on the deck, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0209)
      挂着三面旗的船停在岸边，船上站着官员和士兵
    - Along the river, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0210)
      河岸
    - Houses along canal, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0211)
      运河两岸的房屋
    - Hillside settlement, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0212)
      河边山脚下的一些房屋
    - Gate in busy street, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0213)
      商业街道和城门（光明眼药的招牌）
    - Rural settlement beside canal gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0214)
      运河旁的堤坝和房屋
    - Low pedestrian bridge, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0215)
      河上的人行桥
    - Tributary entrance, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0216)
      河道交汇处
    - Houses beside the canal, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0217)
      河边房屋
    - Cropland, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0218)
      河边农田
    - View along river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0219)
      河岸风景
    - View along river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0220)
      Page 16. Version of RL11422-P-0219
    - Sheaves of bamboo beside storage building, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0221)
      谷仓和一旁的毛竹堆
    - Dock area, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0222)
      繁忙的码头
    - Chinese boat under sail, near bridge, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0223)
      从桥上看河中帆船
    - Houses near dock, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0224)
      码头附近密集的房屋
    - Thatched houses, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0225)
      茅草房
    - Docked Chinese boats with sails, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0226)
      停在码头的帆船
    - Steamboat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0227)
      河面上的汽船
    - Chinese boat docked beside building, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0228)
      正在靠岸的帆船
    - Chinese boat (near), 1890s; 3.875 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0229)
      浅水中的大帆船
    - Five Chinese men on deck of boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0230)
      船上的五个人
    - Chinese boats in bay, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0231)
      河湾处的许多船只
    - Riverbank, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0232)
    - Men pulling boat along bank?, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0233)
      岸边的一排纤夫
    - Dock with crowds of men, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0234)
      码头上的人群
    - Water rushing through canal gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0235)
      运河闸门
    - Chinese boats in bay, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0236)
    - Crowd of men and boys beside building, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0237)
      房屋前的人群
    - Boat with netting, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0238)
      河面上撑着渔网的船只
    - Open canal gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0239)
      河上闸门打开
    - Chinese men in formation, with rifles, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0240)
      一排持枪的团勇
    - Baby, seated in low chair, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0241)
      坐在竹车里的小童
    - Large ferry boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0242)
      大渡船
    - Woman pounding grain, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0243)
      人群中间捶稻谷的妇女
    - Expedition team on road, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0244)
      勘测队在田间
    - Small ferry boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0245)
      小渡船
    - Chinese boats docked at town, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0246)
      镇上码头密集的船只
    - Chinese boats, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0247)
      岸边停靠的船只
    - Chinese boats docked in river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0248)
      码头上停靠的船只
    - Low tide, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0249)
      退潮时的河湾
    - Water rushing under bridge over canal, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0250)
      运河桥下湍急的河水
    - Water rushing under bridge over canal, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0251)
      Page 24. Version of RL11422-P-0250
    - Chinese boat on river, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0252)
      江上船只
    - Chinese boats on river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0253)
    - Group of thirteen Chinese young men, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0254)
      十三名青年男子合影
    - Poles extended to river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0255)
      从岸边伸向河中的长杆
    - Pathway along river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0256)
      河边小路
    - Chinese man on boulders, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0257)
      坐在大石上的男子
    - Rural Chinese town, 1890s; 4 x 4.875 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0258)
    - Crowded dock, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0259)
    - Man and woman, both Westerners, sitting on log, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0260)
      坐在木头上的几个外国男女
    - Chinese boat docked, with crew, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0261)
      停在岸边的一只大船和船上的水手
    - Chinese boat docked next to houses, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0262)
      停在岸边的一只大船
    - Chinese boat, with oars, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0263)
      河上的一只大船，伸入水中的橹
    - Chinese boat, with flag and oars, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0264)
      河上的一只大船，旗杆和伸入水中的橹
    - Chinese boat, with crew, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0265)
      岸边的大船，船上的水手
    - Canal gate with waterfall, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0266)
      运河水闸前的河面水位落差
    - Chinese boat at river, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0267)
    - Four Chinese boats, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0268)
      江上的四艘船
    - Canal gate, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0269)
      运河水闸
    - Chinese boat passing through canal gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0270)
      帆船正通过运河水闸
    - Canal gate, full view, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0271)
      运河水闸全景
    - Chinese boat, after passing through canal gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0272)
      帆船驶出运河水闸
    - Men, women, and children at work on shore, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0273)
      岸边劳作的人群，有男有女有儿童
    - Chinese boat docked at canal gate, three chimneys on next to a building, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0274)
      运河水闸旁停靠的船只，岸上的建筑物旁的三个烟囱